ASIFIWE Emmanuel

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER.

\geq	emmanuel2koestner@gmail.com	+250784619507	9	Kigali, Rwanda		
in https://www.linkedin.com/in/emmanuel-koestner-aa5433110						
	https://emmanuel262.ş	github.io/emmanuel	-asif	iwe/		

SUMMARY

I am currently a fresh graduate of Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering from the University of Rwanda/College of Science and Technology. My ambition is to extend my acquired expertise and Machine learning Innovation principles by self-study and the application of multiple models in order to assist people all over the world.

visit my personal brand to learn more. https://emmanuel262.github.io/emmanuel-asifiwe/

SKILLS

Machine Learning	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ	nodejs	\bullet \bullet \circ \circ
programming Python	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ	programming with	
Mathematics		Matlab	
HTML and CSS	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ	database through mongodb	
JavaScript		Typing	
		iypiiig	

EXPERIENCE

Intern

Rwanda Broadcasting Agency (RBA) Jul 2019 - Sep 2019 Transmission and Energy Engineer

- Transmitting prepared signal to the tower before broadcasting.
- Troubleshooting radio transmitter and receiver devices.
- Accessing different towers to troubleshoot in case of emergence.
- Electrical and Electronics installation inside the main branch of RBA and outside to the towers.

Radio Engineer

- Working as Radio mixers by processing and producing required programs before broadcasting.
- Troubleshooting radios, mixers, microphones in case there is a malfunction.
- Preparing Events required to be broadcasted.

IT

- Streaming the program prepared by another department.
- Connecting different departments by providing access to different resources inside the house.
- Troubleshooting servers, computers, and other devices in case of malfunction.

Intern

Andela Rwanda Nov 2021 - Present

Software engineers who successfully complete the 9-month program will:

- Gain the technical and professional skills demanded by the world marketplace.
- Gain the technical JavaScript skills you need to start your career as a FullStack Junior Developer.
- Get access to Andela's pool of technical mentors.
- Have the fastest track to your employment as a software engineer in the African Tech Ecosystem.

PROJECTS

Coal Mine Monitoring system.

Designer and implementer. Mar 2020 - Present

The coal mine monitoring system by using a wireless sensor network which is composed of multiple sensors has been developed to monitor the surrounding parameters in the underground mine environment such as toxic gases, temperature, humidity, smoking, and collapses of the mining surfaces.

for more info, visit https://github.com/Coal-Mine-Monitoring-System

dsnk_distribution

designer and implementer.

dsnk distribution is a Python module for data science and machine learning that was created with the goal of reducing calculation complexity.

for more info, visit https://github.com/Emmanuel262/dsnk_distributions

EDUCATION

Computer Science and Electronics

ESBF GISENYI Feb 2013 - Nov 2015

A'Level

Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering.

University of Rwanda / College of Science and Technology. Sep 2016 - Jul 2021 Bachelor degree.

LANGUAGES

English	Francais	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$
KINYARWANDA		

AWARDS

AWS Foundation of Machine learning

Udacity 2021-10-22

Introduction to Machine learning

Coursera 2021-08-06

I would advice you to visit my personnal brand for more information and other awards acquired.

REFERRAL

Dr. Louis SIBOMANA

Head of Department, Science, Technology Development and Outreach at NCST, Rwanda.

+250782588422 lewis.sis@gmail.com

Dr Gerard RUSHINGABIGWI

Lecturer at U.R-CST

+250785469187 g.rushingabigwi@gmail.com